dam.com.bd 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - dam.com.bd

### Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
Dam.com.bd Privacy Policy  
Effective Since October 01, 2013

**Scope and Changes:**

dam.com.bd respects your privacy and we want you to be confident in sharing your information with us. This Website Privacy Statement is designed to inform you of the types of information we collect from users, how we use that information, and the circumstances under which we will share it with third parties. This Website Privacy Statement applies only to the Websites. It does not apply to your use of any other websites (whether or not operated by us), including any websites to which we provide links or websites of our partners or advertisers, or to any activities which are not online.Please note that some features and/or services referenced may not be available on some Websites. Therefore, portions of this Website Privacy Statement that pertain to such features or services may not be applicable on each of the Websites. This Website Privacy Statement is effective as of the date listed above. Even if you read and/or agreed to a prior privacy statement, you need to review this updated version. We reserve the right to revise this Website Privacy Statement at any time and at our discretion. If we decide to change our Website Privacy Statement, we will post those changes to this Website Privacy Statement accessible on the homepages of the Websites, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users via either email or by posting a notice on the Websites for 30 days.

**Personal Information and How We Use It**

Generally, you may use some features the Websites without providing us with any personally identifiable information, but on some of our Websites, users have the option of providing various personal information to make the best use of available services and features and certain services and features require that you provide personal information. This section describes what we collect and how we use it. Providing your personal information is always voluntary, and you can always choose not to provide your personal information by choosing not to use the service or feature. By providing your personal information you acknowledge and consent to our use of such information in accordance with this statement. 

**INFORMATION SUBMITTED BY YOU**

Email Address: On some of the Websites, you have the choice of providing your email address if, for example, you would like to receive information from us. 

Account or Profile Information: On some of the Websites, you may be able to become a registered user and create your user profile. When you decide to become a registered user, we ask for some basic contact information, such as a username and email address. You also may choose to provide other information about yourself, either as part of your public profile or otherwise, such as your age, gender or interests. We may use the information that we collect or receive to create a user profile in connection with your account. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences, activities and interactions. 

**Content or Correspondence Submitted By You:**

If you choose to post content on any of the Websites where posting is available (for example, a product or merchant review, or wish list), or submit personal correspondence to dam.com.bd, we may collect and maintain that information in a file specific to you.

Lists: Some of the Websites allow you to create lists of products that are interesting to you. The default for certain lists is for the list to be publicly available. You may change the privacy setting of your lists as provided on the Websites.

**INFORMATION ACQUIRED AUTOMATICALLY**

We collect certain information on the Websites through cookies, web beacons or log files, and we receive information from third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

A cookie is a piece of data tied to information about the user and stored on the user's computer. Web beacons are similar in function to cookies and are used to track the online movements of Web users. We use both session cookies, which terminate when a user closes his browser, and persistent cookies, which remain on the user's computer until manually deleted. We and/or our third party advertisers also use web beacons. 

**Log Files:**

Like most standard website servers we use log files. Log files store information including internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks, and are used to analyze trends, administer the Websites, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use your IP address at times to help identify you as you browse and to gather broad technical and demographic information on who uses our Websites. We do not tie log files to personally identifiable information.

**Third Party Information:**

We may receive information about you from other sources. For example, we may receive product search or purchase information from merchants whose sites you visit after clicking on a product listing on our site, updated delivery and address information from shipping carriers or other third parties, updated or corrected contact information from third party vendors, or credit or related information as part of vendors’ fraud detection services.

**Disclosure**

We don’t sell anything; just give you the information about it. If you don’t get the correct prize as we listed please make confirmation by calling them before you go for the shop. We don't sell or rent users' personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users' explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.

**Security**

We use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. All personal electronic details will be kept private by the Service except for those that you wish to disclose. It is unacceptable to disclose the contact information of others through the Service. If you violate the laws of your country of residence and/or the terms of use of the Service you forfeit your privacy rights over your personal information. 

Physical Address: Office Level#5A, House#206, Road#6, Block B, Bashundhara,

Baridhara, Dhaka-1226

Customer Support e-mail: dam.com.bd@gmail.com 

Customer Support telephone number: +88 0178 77433 78

**Unsubscribe information:**

you agree to receive marketing communications about consumer goods and services on behalf of our third party advertising partners unless you tell us that you prefer not to receive such communications. If at any time you wish to have unsubscribed or your information removed from our active databases, please contact us. Additionally, you will be able to unsubscribe anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all our email communications.
